人人影视
YYeTs.com
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译： 暴龙蛋       圈圈       阿髻
翻译： 胖兔纯     苏小黛     Kiko     DustD
时间轴： 浓子   萌    校对： 苏小黛   胖兔纯
后期： 孤帆    总监： 米小勒   胖兔纯
塞勒姆
第一季  第二集
《塞勒姆》前情提要
Previously on "Salem"...
今天看到一个人风尘仆仆地进城了
Saw a dusty fella walking into town today.
我简直不敢相信自己的眼睛
I couldn't believe my eyes.
是约翰·奥登
It was John Alden.
你告诉我他死了
You told me he was dead!
这就是我的誓言
This is my vow.
为了你我会回来的
I will come back for you.
约翰·奥登比起你眼前的一切算得了什么
What's John Alden compared to all that lies before you?
你回来的目的只有一个
You come back for one thing and one thing only.
如今她可是玛丽·西布里
She's Mary Sibley now.
她是塞勒姆最富有的女人
And she's the richest woman in Salem.
喂食时间到了
Time for your feeding.
塞勒姆因为巫师的事人心惶惶
Precious Salem caught up in a stinking witch panic.
若无一场血战  魔鬼绝不会轻易
The devil was never going to let
让我们在这里建立应许之地
a promised land be built here without a fight!
我不害怕死人
I'm not afraid of the dead,
活人也不怕
nor the living for that matter.
那些可怕的巫师想要什么
What is it that these witches want?
一个属于他们的国家
A country of their own.
我年复一年地一直在等着你
I waited for you. Years and years.
那晚的事我都看到了
I was there the night you did it.
他留给我的只有这个孩子了
It's all that I have left of him.
那是约翰·奥登的孩子
That was John Alden's baby.
你是想自己告诉他呢  还是我来
Are you gonna tell him, or am I?
她会指出女巫是谁
She will show us the witch.
谁看见了我们
Who saw us?
我也再回答你一次
I will tell you again.
我不知道
I do not know.
巫师追捕行动已经开始  而主持审判的会是我们
The witch hunt has begun, and we will be running the trials.
你承认自己有罪
Are you guilty...
或是无罪
or not?
大部分之前活着的人如今都死了
Most of those who have ever lived are now dead.
但有极少数人一定会被地狱之火焚烧
All but very few must surely burn in hell.
我们希望有天这片幅员辽阔的土地能人丁兴旺
We may someday over-people this vast, empty new land,
但恐怕地狱已经先声夺人
but I fear that we have already over-peopled hell.
如此  就如以赛亚书中所述
So that, as it is written in Isaiah,
"阴间扩张其欲"
"Hell hath enlarged herself."
以赛亚书5:14
故此  阴间扩张其欲  开了无限量的口
他们的荣耀  群众  繁华  并快乐的人  都落在其中
如今这里被称作...
And is now called...
美国
America.
我来塞勒姆才两周
I have been in Salem a fortnight,
就已处死了三名巫师
and I have already hung three witches.
建立人间天堂就要付出如此的代价吗
Is this the price of building heaven on earth?
我已将黑手伸向他那些最致命的仆人
I have laid my hands upon his most deadly servants...
那些巫师
the witches.
我到底有没有
Or have I?
我遵从你的每一条命令
I obeyed every one of your instructions.
我甚至逼死了一个可能无辜的男人
I even pressed a possibly innocent man to death.
我依然能尝到他飞溅在我唇上的鲜血
I still taste his spattered blood on my lips.
主啊  我求求你
Please, Lord, I beg thee.
给我一个征兆
Give me a sign.
*擂我战鼓*
*Pound me the witch drums*
*鼓鸣震天*
*Witch drums*
*擂我战鼓*
*Pound me the witch drums*
*鼓鸣震天*
*The witch drums*
*宁入地狱*
*Better pray for hell*
*不留人间*
*Not hallelujah*
原谅我
Forgive me.
你对生活失去性趣了吗
Have you lost your lust for life?
别告诉我你已经玩够了
Don't tell me that you are full up.
或许是某个黑洞欲求不满
Perhaps some holes cannot be filled.
是吗  大人
Really, my lord?
那是什么洞啊
Which holes are those?
那个我们为自己挖的洞
The ones we dig for ourselves.
亲爱的  你的神情为何如此沉重
What weighs so heavy on you, love?
怕我父亲用鞋底抽我
By the taste of it, my father's boot.
你现在是大人了
You're a big boy now.
成熟男人可不怕他们的父亲
Grown men don't fear their fathers.
你又不认识我父亲
You don't know my father.
是个人都认识他
Everyone knows your father.
也对
Precisely.
不  你不能进去
No, you can't go in there!
奥登上尉
Captain Alden!
不  不  不
No! No! No!
放开他
Leave him alone!
滚
Get out.
这就是你赎罪的方法吗
This is how you wipe the innocent blood off your hands?
干得爽吗
On the ass of a whore?
吉尔斯·科里从没为自己辩白过
Giles Corey never pled!
所以我们如何得知他是清白的
Ergo, we don't know he was innocent!
给我一个
Give me one good reason
不杀你的理由
why I don't put you in the ground.
我说不出来
Sir, I cannot.
自我十岁起  我就期望死神的到来
I've been expecting the angel of death since I was 10.
我没亲眼看到过他  但在我祖父临死前
I didn't see him myself, but I knew from the look
我在他的眼神里
in grandfather's eyes just before he went,
看到了死神恐怖的面孔
the angel bore a most terrible face.
正如你现在这样
Quite like yours, I expect.
动手吧  天使
So come, angel.
你会发现我已完全准备好
You find me fully prepared
成为一支人肉蜡烛  和所有那些该死的人一起
to burn like a human candle for eternity
在燃烧着黑焦油的深渊里照亮永恒
in a pit of burning black tar with all the other damned.
燃烧的黑焦油
Burning black tar?
不应该是地狱火吗
I thought hell was fire.
那是种普遍的错误观念
A common misconception.
地狱之火形态似火
Hellfire burns like fire
但其实是粘稠的黑沥青
But is the consistency of thick black pitch.
怎么了
What?
你看到什么了
What have you seen?
不知道
Not sure.
可能是世间的地狱吧
Hell on earth, maybe.
穿好衣服
Get dressed.
我有东西给你看
I've got something to show you.
这是去哪里
Where are we going?
树林
The woods.
去那里干什么
To what end?
虽然你道德败坏如同蝼蚁
You have the moral compass of a meat ant,
但巫师的事你确实知道点
but you do know something about witches.
我看到过他们
I saw them.
就跟梅西·路易丝描述的一样
Just like Mercy Lewis described them.
人体兽头之类的
Animal heads and all.
奥登上尉
Captain Alden.
作为塞勒姆的治安官  我以你昨晚
As magistrate of Salem, I hereby place you under arrest
在绞刑架下的暴力抗议罪逮捕你
for violent remonstrations in the common last night.
你将面临妨碍公共秩序
You shall face charges of disorderly, riotous mischief
和煽动混乱罪的起诉
and incitement to mayhem.
去找艾萨克  他会带你去的
Talk to Isaac. He'll show you the way.
你想怎样  霍尔
What are you gonna do, Hale?
像逼死吉尔斯·科里一样把我逼死吗
Press me to death just like you did to Giles Corey?
这该怪你的牧师新朋友吧
I suggest you take that up with your new friend,
都是他干的  与我无关
the reverend, as it was his doing, not mine.
带他走
Away with him.
你今晚够忙的啊
You've had a busy night.
你打算什么时候告诉我你逮捕了约翰·奥登
When were you planning to tell me you'd arrested John Alden?
把他绞死前还是绞死后呢
Before or after you hang him?
他就是个不定时炸弹
The man is a loose canon.
他在全镇一半的人面前公然威胁镇长
He threatened the selectmen in front of half the town.
如果他是个麻烦  那也是我的麻烦
If he's a problem, he's my problem.
恕我直言
With all due respect,
他可能会成为我们所有人的麻烦
he could become a problem for us all.
塞勒姆我丈夫说了算  而他又对我言听计从
My husband controls Salem, and I control him.
所以我没发话你不许轻举妄动
You do nothing without my say.
无意冒犯
With all due respect.
是  夫人
Yes, ma'am.
你的任务只有一个  霍尔先生
Concern yourself with one thing, Mr. Hale --
找到破坏祭祀圈的人
Find out who broke our circle.
再去树林
Head back to the woods.
找到鬼眼
Find the seer.
他当时有眼线在场
His eyes were there.
我们就是在这里看到巫师的
It was right here we saw the witches.
奥登上尉也看到了吗
Captain Alden saw all this, too?
对
Yeah.
还有别的...
And something else...
我之前从未见过
Something I ain't seen before.
他们刺死了一只鸟
They stabbed a bird --
一只白鸽
A white dove.
我自己杀过不少鸽子
I killed more than a few pigeons myself,
白鸽不过就是只好看点的鸽子
and a dove ain't nothing but a prettier pigeon,
但这次感觉不同
but this felt different.
我也说不上原因
I can't say why...
就好像那是世上最悲伤的事
Like it was the saddest thing in the world...
让一只白鸽血流至死
To bleed a dove to death.
只是一只白鸽
Just the one dove.
果然  就像巫师之釜
Of course. Like a witch's cauldron.
一棵树  像釜
A tree? Like a cauldron?
人们还说我疯了
And folks say Isaac's touched.
找到了
Got you.
西布里夫人
Mrs. Sibley.
-打开  -是  夫人
- Open it. - Yes, ma'am.
退下吧
Now leave.
你的行为在塞勒姆可是要处以绞刑的
Salem still hangs men for what you did...
你威胁了镇长
Threatening the selectmen.
什么都阻止不了他们
Nothing stopping them.
我绝不会让那种事发生的
I'd never let that happen.
那么吉尔斯·科里被大石压死时
And where was that compassion
你那怜悯之心哪去了
when Giles Corey was being crushed to death?
你可以走了
You're free to go.
但是镇长要你离开塞勒姆  永不回来
But the selectmen urge you to leave Salem and never come back.
是镇长要我离开
The selectmen...
还是玛丽·西布里
...or Mary Sibley?
我这是在救你
I am trying to save you.
你不属于这里
You don't belong here.
你也不属于这里
And neither do you.
我告诉过你了  我不能走
I told you... I can't leave.
据我所知
Well, last time I checked,
你丈夫可没那个本事阻止你
your husband was in no shape to stop you.
真没想到你如此自信啊  上尉
Your confidence astounds me, Captain.
你是不是一直想象我会满含喜悦的泪水
But did you imagine that I would welcome you back
欢迎你回来
with tears of joy?
你真是天真啊
How incredibly naive you are.
太晚了
You're too late.
都结束了
It's over.
我不想在这里看到你
I don't want you here.
我差点就相信你了
I almost believe you.
马上离开塞勒姆
Get out of Salem... now...
否则你会被绞死的
Or you will hang.
先生
Sir.
加把劲  你可以的
All right, you can do this.
我做不到
I can't do it.
-太大了  -你可以的
- It's too big. - Yes, you can.
比你小的姑娘都能顺利生下更大的孩子呢
I have gotten bigger babies out of smaller girls.
不能让这个姑娘生下孩子
Not this baby out of this girl,
除非她肯说出孩子父亲的名字
not until she tells us the name of the father.
西布里夫人  恕我直言
Mrs. Sibley, excuse me,
这孩子必须得生下来
but this baby has got to come out.
塞勒姆不会接受这个野种
Salem won't shoulder another bastard.
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
我的朋友布里奇特在教我
My friend Bridget teaches me
上帝造物的神奇
the wonders of God's own creation.
汉娜
Hannah,
把他的名字说出来好吗
will you tell us the name of your man?
我不能说  小姐  否则他就当不成学徒了
I cannot, miss. He'll lose his apprenticeship.
这几年他是不能结婚的
He ain't allowed to marry for some years yet.
那是他的问题  不是塞勒姆的
That is his problem, not Salem's.
玛丽  你也是女人
Mary, you're a woman.
也曾穷困潦倒
You were even a poor one once.
但现在你是玛丽·西布里
But now you're Mary Sibley.
就一次  用你在清教徒中的地位
For once, use your position among the puritans
帮帮自己人吧
to help one of your own.
没有男人值得你如此  孩子
No man is worth it, child,
如果他值得  他就宁愿你说出他的名字
or if he is, he would rather you tell us his name
也不要你为保护他而死
than die trying to protect him.
比利
Billy!
是比利·贝林  桶匠的学徒
It was Billy Bailyn, the cooper's apprentice.
放轻松  听我说
Just relax. Stay with me.
没事的  汉娜
All right, Hannah.
我需要你再用点力
I want you to give me a big push.
就差一点
Almost there!
就这样
That's it.
用力  很好
Big push. Well done!
继续
Keep going.
生出来了
That's it.
救救我
Help me!
没事的
It's going to be all right.
抱歉  夫人
Excuse us, madam.
来吧  进去
Come on, now. In you go.
彼得鲁斯  不是吧
Petrus, really.
你真该挂个铃铛了
You ought to wear a little bell.
而您  治安官大人  就大可不必了
And you, Magistrate, need none.
您一上路我们就听到动静了
We heard you the moment you left the road.
来
Come.
这地方可真不好找
I had a bit of trouble finding the place.
让我记起  上次你还去了更北的地方
Seemed to recall you having been farther north last time.
也许我真去过  霍尔治安官
Perhaps I was, Magistrate Hale.
眼睛是用来洞察
Eyes are for seeing,
而不是被发现的
not for being seen.
这也是你们这种人来找我的原因
That's why your kind come to me.
需要的时候你就会找到我
You find me when you need me.
说吧  这次需要什么
So, what do you need?
昨晚我们在树林里的祭祀圈被破坏了
Someone broke our circle in the woods last night.
我们得知道有谁看见了
We need to know who saw us.
雄鹿满月
Full buck moon?
那晚你在场  是吧  小家伙
You were there that night, weren't you, little friend?
该醒醒了
Time to wake up.
你看见什么了
What did you see?
告诉玛丽·西布里我们会查清
Tell Mary Sibley we will find out
昨晚谁在那片树林里
who was in the woods last night,
但需要时间
but it takes time.
主...
Lord...
我们的祷告有回应了吗
Have our prayers been answered?
这可怜的姑娘好些了吗
Has the poor girl improved?
我们自己能做的事
We should not be praying for God to do
不该恳求上帝完成
what we can accomplish ourselves.
梅西·路易丝所受的折磨并非来自巫师或魔鬼
Mercy Lewis is not suffering the work of witches or demons,
只是自然疾病  或是头脑发烧了
but some natural malady or fever of the mind,
可她却被吊在这里  像牲畜一样
yet she hangs here like an animal.
她在家中三次挣脱绳索
She broke her ropes three times at home,
更不必提她父亲手臂的伤了
not to mention her father's arm.
她咬断自己的手指
She bit off her own finger
撕裂自己的血肉
and tears at her flesh.
必须保护她不能伤害自己和大家
Mercy must be protected from herself and we from her.
没有比上帝之所更适合的地方了
There's no better place to do both than in the house of God.
我认为执行官只是利用她的处境
I think the selectmen are exploiting her condition
在塞勒姆制造恐慌
to create fear in Salem.
这种所谓的"巫师恐慌"
This so-called "witch panic"
只是清教徒试图控制我们的把戏
is yet another attempt by the puritans to control us.
毕谢普小姐  请你...
Miss Bishop, please...
请你注意自己的言辞
Be careful of the words that you speak.
若是让狠心的人听了去
To less sympathetic ears,
会以为这是魔鬼本人在说话呢
they could sound like the words of the devil himself.
很抱歉...我失言了
I'm...sorry if my words were harsh.
我有时候说话不经大脑
Sometimes, my tongue runs ahead of my mind.
可以理解
It's understandable.
这对我们所有人都是种考验
These are trying times for all of us.
小心点  夫人
Careful, mistress.
你的泪水可能会让乳汁酸腐
Your tears may sour the milk.
曾经的我
There was a time
也能哺育其他生命  而不是蟾蜍
that I might have suckled something other than a toad.
现在都无关紧要了
It doesn't matter now.
重要的是  下一个目标是谁
What matters is, who will be next?
大祭典已经开始
The grand rite has begun,
土地渴求着纯洁鲜血的滋养
and the earth cries out for innocent blood.
我很清楚自己的职责
I know well my duties.
顾好你自己吧
Attend to your own.
我的职责就是看好你履行职责
Your duties and seeing that you fulfill them
不管你愿不愿意
is my duty, like it or not.
我已经做出决定了
I've made my choice.
但我们需要的不只是祭品
But we need more than another victim --
还需要一个征兆
We need a sign.
而我正好知道一个人可以同时提供这两者
And I know just the person to deliver us both.
我们的柯顿·麦哲神父对征兆颇为着迷
Our Cotton Mather is quite obsessed with signs --
在他的书里时有提起
wrote chapter and verse on them.
但有一个征兆比其它的都要可怕
But there is one sign they dread more than any other.
那就是畸婴出世
The sign of a monstrous birth.
你做得出这样的事情吗
You would do such a thing?
不  根本不需要我
No, I have no need
亲手从生命之树上摘除那片叶子
to pluck a single leaf from the tree of life
因为它在枝头便已然枯萎
when a leaf is already dead on the branch.
镇里有一个女孩
There's a girl out there
她怀了一个死婴
who carries death inside.
我能闻到它的气味
I could smell the baby,
那个死于母亲腹中的畸形婴儿
floating dead and malformed in her mother's womb.
无需为她惋惜
Don't weep for her.
至少她永远不会尝到被命运背叛的苦涩
She never tasted a single bitter breath of life's betrayals.
而当我将她作为
Yet her brief flicker of life
厄运即将降临塞勒姆的征兆时
will burn like a comet over earth
她转瞬即逝的人生
when I make of her a sign...
将如流星般耀眼
of the doom that's come upon Salem.
你知道我最享受的是什么吗  乔治
Do you know what I enjoy most, George?
让塞勒姆的善良人们如你教导的那般
Turning the good souls of Salem against one another,
像疯狗一样自相残杀
like the rabid dogs you trained them to be.
我活着就是为了有一天
The only thing that keeps me alive
能亲眼见到
is the look on your face
当约翰·奥登发现你真正身份时你脸上的表情
when John Alden finds out what you really are
看着他亲手勒死你
and throttles you with his bare han--
别忘了  乔治
Just think, George.
我只需要在猎月到来之前
I need only kill nine more innocents
再杀死九名无辜者
before full hunter's moon,
我的大祭典就将完成
and my grand rite is complete.
没事的  姬蒂
Shush now, Kitty.
如果那个老胖子弗雷德在床上都没折腾死你
If lying with old fat Fred didn't kill you,
那生他的孩子也一定不会
delivering his child won't, neither.
不  它快将我撕成两半了
No! It feels like it'll tear me in two.
是时候了
It's almost time.
快去叫布里奇特过来
Go fetch Bridget.
布里奇特小姐
Miss Bridget!
我正准备去找你
I was just coming to get you.
我听到她的惨叫了  可怜的姬蒂
I heard poor Kitty's screams.
姬蒂  姬蒂
Kitty, Kitty, Kitty.
这下不用怕了
Nothing to fear now.
布里奇特小姐丰富的接生经验可是无人能比
Miss Bridget's seen more babes through the narrow gate than any.
别害怕孩子  这婴儿只是胎位不正
Don't fret, child. The baby's just the wrong way 'round.
纠正过来很容易的
It is a simple thing to turn it.
不
No!
不要  不要
No! No! No! No!
她在伤害我的孩子
She's hurting my baby!
巫师与幽灵真实存在之证
你亲眼见证了巫师集会
You witnessed a real witches' sabbat --
这是任何巫师猎手
Something no witch hunter
至今都没有机会亲眼见证的
has ever seen with his own eyes.
所有的图像与描述都源于人们的忏悔
All of our images and accounts come from confessions,
只能说  当中有些并不十分可信
some...rather more believable than others.
就是这个
It's this one.
如果这是真的  那情况比我想象的更加严重
If this is true, it's far worse than I thought.
上面说的什么
What's it say?
不认识拉丁文吗  上尉
No Latin, captain?
当然了  你无暇阅读书籍
Oh, of course not. You've no time for books.
"伟大的仪式"
"Ritum Magni."
大祭典
The Grand Rite --
巫师们最大的秘密
The greatest secret of the witches.
目前我们只听说过数次失败尝试的传言
All we have are scraps of rumors of failed attempts.
不幸的是  巫师们从不写书
Unfortunately, there are no books by witches --
只有巫师猎手写的
only witch hunters.
所以说  这么多书
So all of these books...
实际上一无所用
tell you exactly nothing.
住手
Stop it.
如果你们互相争斗
You fight each other.
那谁去对抗他们
Who fights them?
他说得有理
He has a point.
那么  我们从何入手
So, where do we begin?
在那棵树中  我发现了他们汲取能量的来源
Inside the tree, I found what fuels their work...
正如生火需要的薪柴一般
like the wood of a fire.
巫师们的一切巫术都需要两样东西提供能量
See, everything the witch does is powered by two things --
肉欲与死亡
Lust and death.
她们可以靠自身获得肉欲
The lust they provide for themselves,
但必须从别处获得死亡
but they must look elsewhere for the dead parts.
如果塞勒姆的墓地被人破坏的话
The town would be aware if their own Salem burial ground
镇里的人们一定会发现的
was being disturbed by corpse grinding.
那他们要从哪得到它
So where do they get them?
艾萨克  你能好心
Isaac, if you'd be so kind
向上尉解释下你的工作吗
as to explain to the captain your duties.
我有各种工作
I got all kind of duties --
比如说运送包裹
Packages to deliver.
我还负责将被遗弃者运去山壑
I also deliver the unwanteds to the crags.
被遗弃者
The unwanteds?
你知道的  印第安人  奴隶  还有罪犯
You know, Indians, slaves, criminals --
就是那些没有资格葬在塞勒姆墓地的人
pretty much anybody ain't fit to be laid in salem ground.
那就是巫师们收获能量的地方
This is where the witches harvest.
尽管这么说可能会再次挑起你的怒火
And at the risk of another thrashing,
但在那里
it is also your best hope
你才能取回你朋友的尸骨
of reclaiming your friend's remains.
你将他的尸体丢进了山壑
You dumped his body into the crags?!
半个小镇都是吉尔斯·科里一手建起来的
Giles Corey built half this town,
你却把他丢在一条破水沟里吗
And you threw him into a goddamn ditch?!
咱们走
Let's go.
去哪
Where?
去带吉尔斯离开那个鬼地方
To get Giles out of that shithole.
整个塞勒姆都为你的损失感到悲痛
All of salem is diminished by your loss.
我无法想象你有多么痛苦
I can only imagine your suffering.
谢谢您  西布里夫人
Thank you, Mrs. Sibley.
他们说你很害怕
The others said that you were frightened...
你以为有人想害你的孩子
You thought that someone was trying to hurt your baby?
跟我说说怎么回事
Tell me what happened.
说吧
Tell me.
我先告诉你一些事
I'm going to tell you something.
我从来没告诉过任何人
I've never told anyone before.
我也失去过一个孩子
I, too, have lost a child.
我了解你那种痛楚
Oh, I know the pain you feel.
时至今日  我仍心如刀绞
I feel it even now.
你一定得告诉我发生了什么
You must tell me what happened
这样你的孩子才不会白白死去
So that your child did not die in vain.
我向你保证
I promise you...
不会有人伤害你的
No harm will come to you.
告诉我吧
Tell me.
我感觉到了恶魔的存在
I felt the presence of evil...
并且...
And...
继续说
Go on.
我看到了一个邪恶的女巫
...I saw a foul hag.
她抚摸着我的肚子
And she was touching my belly.
那助产士呢
What of the midwife?
她怎么了
What of her?
她们是同一个人
They were one and the same.
一天来两次  还是晚上
Two times in as many nights?
这鬼地方根本不是人该来的
Two times too many.
带路  你把他的尸体扔哪了
Show me where you dumped his body.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
他在哪
Where is he?
那边
There.
别拿你的脏手碰他
You do not lay a hand on that man.
抱歉
Oh, forgive me.
正常情况下应该是乔治来的
Ordinarily, this would be George's domain,
但我丈夫...他的情况...
But my husband... his condition...
这东西我怕他只看一眼都会心脏骤停
I fear that the very sight of this would stop his heart.
西布里夫人
Mrs. Sibley, please...
请冷静
Calm yourself.
怎么了
What is wrong?
最糟糕的事情发生了
Oh, a most terrible thing...
一个征兆
A sign.
征兆
A sign?
没错  就像你书里描述的一样
Yes, just as you described in one of your books.
畸婴出世
A monstrous birth.
什么
What?
在塞勒姆吗
Here in salem?
由我们的助产士亲手接生
Delivered by our very own midwife...
布里奇特·毕谢普
Bridget Bishop.
这个...
And where is ...
这个怪物现在在哪
What has become of this monster now?
它在哪
Where is it?
就在这个房间里
In this very room.
兰姆先生把它泡在了一个瓶子里  我...
Mr. Lamb floated it in a bottle. I...
多苦多难的上帝啊
By the wounds of Christ!
这景象  哪怕只是一瞥
The mere sight of this would
便足以再次狠狠伤害他
pierce our dear lord yet again!
您找我来是对的
You were right to send for me.
这真是太恐怖了
This is most terrible.
这预示着什么
But what does it portend?
这是什么征兆
What is this a sign of?
毫无疑问
There can be no doubt.
这一切就是魔鬼本人
'tis nothing less than a declaration of war upon us
在向我们宣战
by the devil himself.
牧师
Reverend...
我们能做什么吗
Is there anything we can do?
我会竭尽所能
I will do whatever is in my power
保护塞勒姆
to protect Salem...
和您  夫人
and you, madam.
感谢上帝你在这里  牧师
I thank God you're here, reverend.
若没有你  我们真不知如何是好了
We would be lost without you.
父亲  请等等
Father, please wait.
父亲  您认识布里奇特
Father, you know Bridget.
您怎能认为她犯下了这种罪孽
How could you think her guilty of this?
我怎么认为无关紧要
It isn't a matter of what I think.
父亲
Father.
又一次草率的审判吗  麦哲
Another rush to judgment, Mather?
恐怕正相反
Quite the contrary, I fear.
是上帝的最后审判正在向我们逼近
It is judgment that is rushing towards all of us.
请看证据
Behold the warrant of judgment.
无论是个人  还是我们共同的罪恶
For our sins, individual and collective,
他代表着撒旦的印记
he has signed the seal of Satan,
一个来自地狱的讯息
a message straight from hell
宣告着恶魔在塞勒姆的降临
to herald the arrival of the devil in Salem.
那么是谁为他传达的信息呢
And who delivered his message for him?
布里奇特·毕谢普
Bridget Bishop.
你是否
Did you or did you not
从那女孩身体里接生了这个怪物
deliver this monster from that girl?
是的  可是...
Yes, but..
你是否
Did you or did you not
在她带孕期间一直照料着她
minister to this girl while she carried it?
是的先生  可我照顾...
Yes, sir, but I minister...
你是否
Did you or did you not
时常喂她服食一些药品和药剂
Frequently dose her with physics and potions
和自制的混合草药汤给她服用
and herbal concoctions of your own devising?
先生  是我做的  但是我没有
Sir, that is what I do, but I did not --
你有没有把你的手放在她的肚子上
And did you or did you not place your hands upon her belly,
如此这般按压
pressing this way and that
就在它出来之前
just before the thing came out?
我在变化胎儿的位...
I was turning the babe so --
没错  把胎儿变成了什么
Aye, but turning it into what?
够了
Stop!
不管那个石婴是什么
Whatever that poor stone child may be,
你才是真正的怪物
you are the true monster!
我为小女道歉
I apologize for my daughter.
被告是她的亲密好友
The accused is a dear friend of hers.
不过我和她持有同样的疑惑
But I share her concern.
你指控的是一个
You would accuse a woman --
我们都熟悉并信赖
a woman whom we all know and trust,
一心帮助其他妇女
who never did anything but help other women
为她们接生
to deliver their babies
照料弃婴的女人
and care for those who no one wanted?
现在突然要我们相信她是个女巫吗
And now, suddenly, we're to believe she's a witch?
恶魔很耐心
The devil is patient.
它的仆人也是如此
And so are his servants --
可能是我们的朋友  可能是邻居
our friends, our neighbors --
直到恶魔召唤他们来服侍
Till, finally, they are called to serve him.
布里奇特·毕谢普
Bridget Bishop,
你助畸婴出世
You have delivered a monster into the world.
被受害者看穿了你的真正面目
You were seen in your true guise,
一个邪恶的老巫婆
the night hag, by your victim.
就算是那些曾经被你无辜形象蒙骗的人们
And even those who were duped by your innocent image
仍然能感受到明显的恶魔阴影围绕着他们
could still sense the palpable stench of evil around them,
因为你毁灭了
as you destroyed
一个未出生的婴儿
a babe in the cradle of life --
这是你的主人向我们宣战的征兆
a sign of your master's declaration of war upon us.
你认罪吗
How do you plead?
我没做过这样的事
I did no such thing.
我是无辜的
I'm innocent!
您得相信我  我
Oh, you must belive me -- I am --
我有点困惑  麦哲
I'm a little confused, Mather.
是布里奇特制造了那个征兆
Did Bridget make that sign...
还是上帝
or did God?
不对  等等  我记起来了
No. No, no, no. Wait. I remember.
上帝告知恶魔  恶魔迫使她这么做
God told the devil, and the devil made her do it --
我说的对不对
have I got this right?
不对吗  可能是我没有你那么聪明
No? Maybe I'm just not as smart as you.
我虽不像你读过那么多书
I haven't read all those books,
但我也算见识了不少市面
but I have seen a few things in the world.
在这个世界上  坏事时有发生
And in this world, bad things happen,
如同掷骰子一般  并说明不了什么
generally with no more meaning than the roll of a dice.
这个怪物
This monstrosity --
只是上帝掷的一次不幸的骰子吗
it's just an unlucky roll of god's dice?
可能是我见过最不幸的一次
Probably the unluckiest I've seen.
那我们的想法真是非常不同
Well, then, we have a most profound difference of opinion.
确实
We do.
但是你只根据你的想法就要绞死一个女人
But you would hang a woman on your opinion.
那根据你的想法  就任由恶魔的使徒
And on yours, you would let an agent of the devil himself
横行并犯下更多罪过吗
walk free to do more malice.
那你也得审问她
Then put her on trial, too.
不能只审一人就完事
Don't just stop there.
她们当时都在场
There were others with her.
可能她们都有责任
Or maybe they're all responsible.
不行  你不能这样  不是我的错
No, you can't! It's not my fault!
不是你的错吗
It's not your fault?
不  我想你可能说得对
No, I think that you're probably right.
我知道对你来说难以置信  麦哲
I think -- and I know this is unthinkable to you, Mather --
但是可能  这不是任何人的错
But maybe, just maybe, it's no one's fault.
而我们都知道  杀人不同
We all know that killing is different.
杀人一定有肇事者
Killing is always someone's fault.
吉尔斯·科里尸骨未寒
The stones aren't dry from the blood of Giles Corey,
现在你又要绞死一个女人
And now you are willing to hang a woman --
这个女人  布里奇特·毕谢普
This woman, bridget bishop --
或许再加上几个妓女
and, hell, throw in a few whores for good measure --
这都为了什么
and for what?
或许我们该听听梅西怎么说
Perhaps it's time we heard from Mercy.
不对吗  麦哲牧师
Isn't that right, reverend Mather?
她不是一定会
Isn't she bound to react
在有罪的巫师面前有所反应的吗
in front of the guilty witch or witches?
我父亲和所有专家同意
My father and all the experts agree --
那就将她们带到她面前
Then take them to her.
她们
Them?
奥登上尉说得很对
Captain Alden is quite right.
所有人都可能有罪
All may be guilty.
把助产士和三个妓女带到她面前
Take the midwife and the three whores, too.
可以投票了吗
Shall we vote?
主啊
Lord...
您知晓我们不为人知的内心
You who sees and knows our secret hearts
您一定知道我是无辜的
must know that I am innocent.
拜托  拜托  拜托  请给他们
Please, please, please give them
一些启示  揭露这个简单的真相
some visible sign of this simple truth.
求求您
Please.
干得好
Well done.
你又杀了一个无辜的人
Another innocent killed.
我不这么认为
I do not think so.
即便我真的滥杀了无辜
But even if I did...
就让主把这个
let the lord add it
也加入我那已经长长的罪恶清单上去吧
to my already lengthy list of mortal sins.
我必须不惜一切代价
I must pay any price,
撒上我自己或他人的血都要阻止那些巫师
spill my own or any other's blood to stop the witches.
我还从来没见过这样一位
I don't think I've ever seen such a mixture
集理智与狗屎于一身的人
of reason and bullshit in a man.
如果你能知我所知
If you only knew what I know...
怎样
What?
我就会压死一个男人  吊死个女人
I'd crush a man or hang a woman,
喝个酩酊大醉
then drink myself blind
然后跟妓女翻云覆雨  誓死方休吗
and bury myself into a whore like there's no tomorrow?
如果我们不阻止这些邪恶的女巫
If we do not stop these foul hags,
那我们就不会有明...
there will be no tomorr--
你个禽兽
You monster!
住手
Stop!
看你把事情搞得多乱
What a mess you've made of things.
就因为你放不下那个男人
We were nearly ruined by a single sound argument
我们差点被他那通反驳坏了大事
from a man you can't seem to let alone.
我开始质疑为何让你这么做
I question now why we let you begin this.
为什么
Why?
因为这是我们所有人的梦想
Because this is the fulfillment of all our dreams --
报复几个世纪以来的镇压
vengeance for centuries of oppression.
现在动摇太晚了  霍尔
Too late for doubts now, Hale.
咱们已经是一股绳子上的了
We are all in this together.
是啊  这样下去咱们定会一起被烧死
Yes, and we shall all burn together at this rate.
你太年轻了  不理解你所经受的风险
You're too young to understand the risk you're taking.
我看着我全家人烧死在柱子上
I saw my entire family burned at the stake.
我亲口尝到了他们骨灰的味道
I tasted their ashes in my mouth.
我没有兴趣去品尝我自己的
I have no desire to taste my own...
亦或是我女儿的
or my daughter's.
也许你们这些旧世界巫师
Well, perhaps you old-world witches
只是过于胆怯
are simply too scared
没有魄力去统治这个新世界
or too scarred to claim this new world.
但我不会
Not me.
我不是一个人
I'm not alone.
元老们也心有动摇
The elders have their doubts, too.
你的恐惧完全没有必要
All your fears are unnecessary.
无辜之血将继续流淌
Innocent blood flows and will continue to flow.
结果  霍尔先生  那才是最重要的
Results, Mr. Hale, are all that matter.
而说到结果
And speaking of results,
你该做的事进行得如何了
What of your errand?
彼得鲁斯说很快就会找出目击者
Petrus assures us we'll soon know who saw us.
抱歉  霍尔小姐
Oh, um...sorry, Miss Hale,
但是  你知道规矩的
But, uh, you know the rules.
这个
There's, uh,
女人天黑后禁止入内
no women allowed after dark.
没事的  兰博
It's all right, Lamb.
据麦哲说  终结即将来临
According to Mather, these are the end times.
我想今晚可以开个特例
I think we can make an exception for tonight.
你在看什么
What are you looking at?
你和他们一样
You're just like them --
喜欢高谈阔论  唇枪舌剑
happy to discuss and debate,
却从不敢真正行动起来
but too afraid to take any real action.
你还在塞勒姆干什么
Why are you even in Salem?
他们杀死你朋友那晚
Where's that fire I saw in your eyes
我在你眼中看到的怒火去哪了
the night they killed your friend?
你想让我干什么  霍尔小姐
What do you want from me, Miss Hale?
正义
Justice --
为吉尔斯·科里  为布里奇特·毕谢普
for Giles Corey, for Bridget Bishop,
还为了这场即将到来的混乱中
and for all the other innocent victims
更多的无辜受害者们
soon to come from this madness.
必须有人来做些什么
Someone must do something!
怎么了
What?
你让我想起了曾经认识的一个人
You just remind me of someone I once knew.
他们怎么了
What happened to them?
真希望我能知道
I wish I knew.
不请自来
Here uninvited --
你一定是和印第安人呆太久了
You must have stayed too long with the indians.
让你变得更像...
It's made you more...
野蛮人了
savage.
不  只是更没有耐心而已
No. Less patient.
有些事我认为你需要知道
There's something I think you should know.
你要离开塞勒姆
You're leaving Salem?
正相反
To the contrary.
安·霍尔提醒了我塞勒姆不应如此
Anne Hale reminded me Salem deserves better.
该做出些改变了
It always did.
真的
Really?
我还以为你厌恶这地方
I thought you hated this place.
我本也这么想
I thought so, too.
但结果发现我恨的不是塞勒姆
But it turns out it wasn't Salem that I hated --
而是控制他的那些人
Rather, the people who run it.
今天有人和我说了一些事情
Fella told me something today --
他说这种景象
he said it was a damn sight easier
破坏比修复要简单得多
to break things than to fix them.
而你想要来进行修复
And you intend to fix things.
也许吧
Maybe.
你准备怎么做
How do you plan on doing that?
行政委员的位子还空着一个
There's an extra seat on the board of selectmen --
一个属于奥登家族的位子
a seat with the Alden name.
也许是时候我来接手了
Reckoned maybe it was time I claimed it.
一个人的声音尽管微弱
Might just be one voice,
但这是个开始
but it is a start.
我们还会再见的
I'll be seeing you.
走开  猫咪
Go away, cat.
你会弄坏我作品的
You'll ruin my work.